[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturns largest moon is known by what name?", "correct_answer": "Titan", "incorrect_answers": ["Europa", "Ganymede", "Cronus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This former baseball player, born in Donora, Pa, has 3630 hits in his career - 1815 hits at home and 1815 hits on the road.", "correct_answer": "Stan Musial", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Thomas", "Ken Griffey, Jr.", "Ken Griffey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Young Noah Calhoun, a character from the movie The Notebook, is instantly smitten with seventeen-year-old Allie Hamilton, when he spots her at a carnival. What is the first thing Noah says to Allie?", "correct_answer": "Would you like to dance?", "incorrect_answers": ["Would you like to go out with me?", "Would you like to ride with me on the Ferris Wheel?", "Would you like to go for a walk?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first industrial production of cheese in the world started in 1815,  in which country?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "France", "Austria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Bessie from The Fighting Temptations movie want to buy when she becomes rich and famous?", "correct_answer": "A Benz", "incorrect_answers": ["A house with an outdoor swimming pool", "A Chinese restaurant", "100 pounds of chocolate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many different species of dolphins are there in the world?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["15", "48", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Selachophobia is the fear of this sea creature.", "correct_answer": "shark", "incorrect_answers": ["octopus", "fish", "crab"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did the Broadway actors brother die in the 2004 movie Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "He was killed by gorillas at a zoo", "incorrect_answers": ["He was killed by muggers", "He was shot while robbers were robbing a store", "He was kidnapped and killed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One the worlds largest silver nuggets was found in Colorado.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what time in a womans life is she most likely to gain the most weight?", "correct_answer": "During pregnancy", "incorrect_answers": ["After the age of 60", "Before her menstruation", "During menopause"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Manny and Ellies daughter that is born in Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "Peaches", "incorrect_answers": ["Berry", "Strawberry", "Melonie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two of these are produced when an acid and a base are mixed together?", "correct_answer": "water and a salt", "incorrect_answers": ["water and another base", "HCl and NaOH", "water and another acid"]}]